export const QuizData = [
    {
      question : "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
      options : ["Virtual DOM", "Original DOM","Both A & B", "None of the Above"],
      answer : 1
    },

    {
      question : "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
      options : ["Render with arguments", "setState", "PropTypes", "props"],
      answer : 4
    },

    {
      question : "Who created React.js?",
      options : ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim Lee", "Jordan Lee"],
      answer : 2
    },

    {
      question : "In which language is React.js written?",
      options : ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "PHP"],
      answer : 2
    },

    {
      question : "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
      options : ["3000", "3306", "3030", "8080"],
      answer : 4
    },

    {
      question : "The CSS property used to set the indentation of the first line in a block of text is",
      options : ["text-indent property", "text-stroke property", " text-decoration property", "text-overflow property"],
      answer : 1
    },

    {
      question : "The correct syntax to give a line over text is",
      options : ["text-decoration: line-through", "text-decoration: none", "text-decoration: overline", " text-decoration: underline"],
      answer : 3
    },

    {
      question : "Which of the following CSS property creates a clipping region and specifies the visible area of the element?",
      options : ["visibility property", " background-clip property", "clip-path property", "None of the above"],
      answer : 3
    },

    {
      question : "Which of the following CSS property is used to represent the overflowed text which is not visible to the user?",
      options : ["text-shadow", "text-stroke", "text-overflow", "text-decoration"],
      answer : 3
    },

    {
      question : "The CSS property used to set the maximum width of the element's content box is",
      options : ["max-width property", "height property", "max-height property", "position property"],
      answer : 1
    },

  ];